We should be encouraging everybody to be authentic at all times.
And you don't lose anything worth having.
If you got to be fake to keep it, it's not worth it.
Period.
Like we live in a fake world where shit is a whole lie all the damn time.
So if you fake, you're a part of the lie.
And then you shouldn't be complaining about shit.
Exactly.
Right?
So it's like the only way that we will make anything change is to change ourselves first.
That is literally the only way.
I really just want to herald.
Like it's almost as if I want to, I'm like, I don't even want us to consider not being authentic.
Like I don't even want that to even be a consideration at this point.
Like I feel that on a very, very simple solution level, if you can just keep it a buck with yourself,
that opens so many glorious doors and opportunities for us shifting this axis of evil that we're in
because it is rooted in lies.
It's rooted in prevarication.
Yeah.
So because of that, so like I'm always looking at the root.
Like I was just watching a video earlier today of this woman who is running against the incumbent,
I believe, in one of these states.
And she's talking about, and what she was saying was very true.
She was like, you know, we need to be able to have Medicare for all, like healthcare for all.
Like we need to be like, because, you know, for those of y'all who are watching in the United States,
we don't have healthcare for all, and it's crazy how much they argue about this.
And everything she was saying was legit.
And people in the comments are like, that's right.
And she was like, we need to get people in office who are going to fight for this.
That's right.
And I'm just like, yes.
Yes.
How also, also.
We're not being honest about how far up the impediment to that goes.
And that is imperative for us to be able to make real solutions.
If you think that just being elected to the house is going to cause the real solutions, it's not.
So we have to be doing that and also acknowledging what is controlling who's elected to governor, to the house, to local governments, to school boards, committees, et cetera.
Because by the way, it's, it's not just on a federal level here or in the UK, right?
It's top down.
Thank you for watching.
Like, comment, share, and subscribe.